[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Relying on a hand crank for power, this gun is considered the first machine gun since it could fire continuously.", "correct_answer": "Gatling gun", "incorrect_answers": ["Maxim gun", "Carronade", "Howitzer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which type of doctor deals with removing hemorrhoids?", "correct_answer": "Proctologist", "incorrect_answers": ["Endocrinologist", "Urologist", "Vascular surgeon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which line of the palm is traditionally examined first by palm readers?", "correct_answer": "Heart line", "incorrect_answers": ["Life line", "Sun line", "Mercury line"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these movies starred George Clooney, Brad Pitt and Frances McDormand?", "correct_answer": "Burn After Reading", "incorrect_answers": ["Oceans Eleven", "Thelma and Louise", "Oceans Twelve"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The mean distance between the Sun and the Earth is about 93 million miles, which is also called what by astronomers?", "correct_answer": "Astronomical Unit (AU)", "incorrect_answers": ["Light Year (LY)", "Solar Constant (SC)", "Astronomical Mile (AM)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What device ignited the bomb that killed sir Robert King in The World Is Not Enough?", "correct_answer": "Collar pin", "incorrect_answers": ["Mobile phone", "Reading glasses", "Wristwatch"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does Willy Wonka want from Charlie in order to make him the heir of his factory in Charlie and the Chocolate Factory 2005?", "correct_answer": "To give up his family", "incorrect_answers": ["To find and kill Willys father", "To stop brushing his teeth", "To resign himself to eating only chocolate for the rest of his life"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Lightning Mcqueen was the protagonist of what movie?", "correct_answer": "Cars", "incorrect_answers": ["BAR", "Mcqueen Tales", "DDA"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of alcohol is traditionally used for the preparation of Pi\u00f1a Colada?", "correct_answer": "Rum", "incorrect_answers": ["Tequila", "Gin", "Vodka"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many biological children does fictional character Vito Corleone have?", "correct_answer": "Four", "incorrect_answers": ["Five", "Two", "Three"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Venus was mistaken for a UFO.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If your physician tells you that you have Presbycusis due to the normal process of aging, he may suggest that you need which of these?", "correct_answer": "Hearing aid", "incorrect_answers": ["Dentures", "Glasses", "A wheelchair"]}]